Guide to the J. E. Wallace Sterling, President of Stanford University, Papers
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Foreign Student Advisor, 1961-1966 (Box B5, Folder 34)
    Bechtel International Student Center included.
  - Law School, 1964-1967 (Box B5, Folder 35)
  - Law School, 1964-1966 (Box B5, Folder 36)
  - Law School - recruiting faculty, 1964-1965 (Box B5, Folder 37)
  - Law School - Board of Visitors, 1963-1966 (Box B6, Folder 1)
  - Libraries, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 2)
  - Libraries, 1966-1967 (Box B6, Folder 3)
  - Mathematics Teachers, 1963 (Box B6, Folder 4)
    Speech given to Dr. Bacon
  - Medical School - Visiting Committee, 1966 (Box B6, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, 1964-1965 (Box B6, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, 1965-1966 (Box B6, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, 1966-1967 (Box B6, Folder 8)
  - Medicare - King-Anderson Bill, 1962 (Box B6, Folder 9)
  - Military Science, Dept. of, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 10)
    ROTC information
  - Munson, Edwin. S, 1964 (Box B6, Folder 11)
    Faculity File - Dept. of Anesthesia at the School of Medicine
  - Paulhe, Peter G., 1964 (Box B6, Folder 12)
    Faculty File - Dept. of Medicine at the School of Medicine
  - Modern European Languages, Dept. of, 1961-1966 (Box B6, Folder 13)
    Stanford in Germany and University of Bucharest program included
  - Music, Dept. of, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 14)
  - Music, Dept. of - Band, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 15)
  - Naval Science, Dept. of, 1962-1964 (Box B6, Folder 16)
  - News and Publications, 1962-1966 (Box B6, Folder 17)
  - Nursing, School of, 1959-1962 (Box B6, Folder 18)
  - Personnel Office, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 19)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 20)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 21)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of, 1964-1967 (Box B6, Folder 22)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of - Football, 1964-1966 (Box B6, Folder 23)
    File on Reunions - 1964 included
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of - Football, 1965 (Box B6, Folder 24)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of - Football, 1967 (Box B6, Folder 25)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of - Rose Bowl, 1966 (Box B6, Folder 26)
  - Medical School, 1964-1965 (Box B6, Folder 1)
  - Medical School - Genetics Dept., 1960 (Box B6, Folder 2)
  - Medical School, 1956-1964 (Box B6, Folder 3)
  - Medical School - Hospital Board, 1961-1962 (Box B6, Folder 4)
  - Medical School - Hospital Board (Dean Bowker's material), 1962-1963 (Box B6, Folder 5)
  - Medical School - Pharmacology Dept., 1960 (Box B6, Folder 6)
  - Medical School - Physiology Dept., 1960-1963 (Box B6, Folder 7)
  - Medical School - Biochemistry Dept., 1960 (Box B6, Folder 8)
  - Physical Education and Athletics, Dept. of - Financial Aids, 1960-1964 (Box B7, Folder 1)
  - Big Game Ticket Record, 1964 (Box B7, Folder 2)
  - President's Courtesy List - Stanford Football, 1959-1964 (Box B7, Folder 3)
  - Athletics, Dept. of - Athletic Board, 1963-1966 (Box B7, Folder 4)
  - Athletics, Dept. of - John Ralston, 1962-1963 (Box B7, Folder 5)
    Considered for the coaching position
  - Physical Education, Dept. of - Women, 1962-1964 (Box B7, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education, Dept. of - Women, 1963-1966 (Box B7, Folder 7)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 1958-1966 (Box B7, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Placement Service, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 9)
  - Planning Office, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 10)
    Space administration and specific building funds
  - Police and Fire Department, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 11)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 1963-1966 (Box B7, Folder 12)
  - President's Office, 1960-1965 (Box B7, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University Press, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 14)
  - Associate Provost and Dean of Research, 1966 (Box B7, Folder 15)
  - Office of the Vice President and Provost, 1962-1966 (Box B7, Folder 16)
  - Office of the Vice President and Provost, 1966-1967 (Box B7, Folder 17)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 18)
  - Associate Provost for Research, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 19)
    Includes a copy of a manuscript "The Undergraduate at Stanford" written in 1965 - taking the place of "Let's Talk"
  - Publications Service, 1965-1966 (Box B7, Folder 20)
  - Quantitative Research Laboratory in Education, 1961 (Box B7, Folder 21)
  - Religious Studies, Dept. of, 1966-1967 (Box B7, Folder 22)
  - Religious Studies, Dept. of - Memorial Church, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 23)
  - Religious Studies, Dept. of, 1962-1966 (Box B7, Folder 24)
  - Registrars Office, 1966-1967 (Box B7, Folder 25)
  - Registrars Office, 1960-1963 (Box B7, Folder 26)
  - Residences and Dining Halls, 1959-1966 (Box B7, Folder 27)
  - Safety Office, 1960-1966 (Box B7, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of the University, 1965-1966 (Box B7, Folder 29)
  - Sociology, Dept. of, 1964-1966 (Box B7, Folder 30)
  - Stanford University Southern California Office, 1959-1964 (Box B7, Folder 31)
  - Speech and Drama, Dept. of, 1962-1966 (Box B7, Folder 32)
  - Speech and Drama, Dept. of - Debate Team, 1966 (Box B7, Folder 33)
  - Speech and Drama, Dept. of - Radio and Television, 1958-1965 (Box B7, Folder 34)
  - Actors Workshop, 1963 (Box B7, Folder 35)
    An alliance between Stanford University and the San Francisco Actor's Workshop.
  - Speech and Drama, Dept. of - Debate Team, 1960-1964 (Box B8, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Overseas Program- Suggestions Additional Campus Locations, 1962-1965 (Box B8, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Overseas Program - Director, 1966 (Box B8, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Overseas Program, 1966-1967 (Box B8, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Overseas Program, 1961-1966 (Box B8, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Overseas Program - Campus Visitors, 1960-1965 (Box B8, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Overseas Program- Stanford in Austria, 1964-1966 (Box B8, Folder 7)
    Includes color photos of the Pauleaus Hotel (?) Austria
  - Stanford Overseas Program - Stanford in Britain, 1963-1966 (Box B8, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Overseas Program- Stanford in Germany, 1962-1966 (Box B8, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Overseas Program - Stanford in France, 1959-1966 (Box B8, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Overseas Program - Stanford in Italy, 1960-1966 (Box B8, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Overseas Program - Advanced Language Program at Nantes, 1965-1966 (Box B8, Folder 12)
  - Statistics, Dept. of, 1959-1965 (Box B8, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session, 1962-1965 (Box B8, Folder 14)
  - TresidderBoxOffice, 1962-1964 (Box B8, Folder 15)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 1965 (Box B8, Folder 16)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union, 1964-1965 (Box B8, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Education, 1964-1966 (Box B8, Folder 18)
  - Old Union Building, 1963-1966 (Box B8, Folder 20)
    Union women's dorm closed in 1965 and remodeled as administrative offices
  - Unique, 1957-1961 (Box B8, Folder 21)
    "Crackpot" letters
  - University Relations, 1961-1966 (Box B8, Folder 22)
  - University Relations - Radio, T.V. and Motion Picture Center, 1961-1963 (Box B8, Folder 23)
  - Grants Expired - Miscellaneous, 1944-1948 (Box B9, Folder 1)
  - Grants Expired - American Cancer Society, 1946-1948 (Box B9, Folder 2)
  - Grants Expired - American Foundation for High Blood Pressure; American Foundation for Tropical Medicine; American Philosophical Society, 1944-1949 (Box B9, Folder 3)
  - Grants Expired - American Medical Association, 1946-1948 (Box B9, Folder 4)
  - Grants Expired - Brush Foundation, 1944-1949 (Box B9, Folder 5)
  - Grants Expired - Bureau of Intercultural Education, 1944-1946 (Box B9, Folder 6)
  - Grants Expired - Carnegie Corporation, 1944-1949 (Box B9, Folder 7)
  - Grants Expired - Columbia Foundation, 1945-1947 (Box B9, Folder 8)
    Community Leadership Workshop
  - Grants Expired - Columbia Foundation, 1943-1944 (Box B9, Folder 9)
    International Education, Dr. G. Kefauver
  - Grants Expired - Columbia Foundation, 1941-1950 (Box B9, Folder 10)
    Miscellaneous correspondences included
  - Grants Expired - Comm. for Economic Stability; Commonwealth Fund; Cutter Laboratories, 1944-1945 (Box B9, Folder 11)
  - Grants Expired - Ford Foundation, 1951-1952 (Box B9, Folder 12)
    Survey in Asian Studies - Carl B. Spaeth
  - Grants Expired - Ford Foundation, 1952 (Box B9, Folder 13)
    Administrative Grant
  - Grants Expired - Ford Foundation, 1952 (Box B9, Folder 14)
    Behavioral research - Kenneth Arrow; Douglas Lawence; Ithiel Pool
  - Grants Expired - Ford Foundation, 1951 (Box B9, Folder 15)
    Institute of Research in Economic Development - denied
  - Grants Expired - Ford Foundation, 1953 (Box B9, Folder 16)
    Institutional Exchange Grant
  - Grants Expired - Inter-American Affairs, 1944-1945 (Box B9, Folder 17)
    Latin American Workshop included
  - Grants Expired - Life Insurance Medical Research Fund, 1946-1949 (Box B9, Folder 18)
  - Grants Expired - John and Mary R. Markle Foundation, 1941-1948 (Box B9, Folder 19)
  - Grants Expired - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1946-1949 (Box B9, Folder 20)
  - Grants Expired - Nutrition Foundation, 1943-1948 (Box B9, Folder 21)
  - Grants Expired - Phillips Petroleum Company, 1944-1945 (Box B9, Folder 22)
  - Grants Expired - Research Corporation, 1945-1948 (Box B9, Folder 23)
  - Grants Expired - Rockefeller Foundation, 1939-1948 (Box B9, Folder 24)
  - Grants Expired - Rockefeller Foundation, 1946-1950 (Box B9, Folder 25)
    Laura Spelman Fund - Research in Social Science
  - Grants Expired - Rosenberg Foundation, 1939-1947 (Box B9, Folder 26)
  - Grants Expired - U.S. Public Health Service, 1946-1949 (Box B9, Folder 27)
  - Grants Expired - Viking Fund, 1943-1948 (Box B9, Folder 28)
  - Gifts - Medical Alumni Fund, 1951-1953 (Box B10, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - Jackling Gifts, 1952 (Box B10, Folder 2)
    Photos of the three Oriental statues and the Ming jardinniere
  - Prospective Gifts - Chronological, 1950-1952 (Box B10, Folder 3)
  - Estates and Wills, 1952-1954 (Box B10, Folder 4)
  - Prospective Gifts A-I, 1947-1953 (Box B10, Folder 5)
  - Prospective Gifts J - Z, 1945-1953 (Box B10, Folder 6)
  - Non-Monetary Gifts, 1951-1954 (Box B10, Folder 7)
  - Stanford University Fund, 1953-1954 (Box B10, Folder 8)
  - Gifts - Lists, 1937-1950 (Box B10, Folder 9)
    Summary of Futures in Expectancy
  - Gifts - Luce, Henry R., 1952 (Box B10, Folder 10)
    Asian Studies, Hoover Institution and Library
  - Gifts - General Data, 1949-1954 (Box B10, Folder 11)
  - Gifts - Anonymous, 1944-1953 (Box B10, Folder 12)
  - Gifts - A, 1944-1953 (Box B10, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - B, 1937-1953 (Box B10, Folder 14)
  - Gifts - C, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 15)
  - Gifts - D, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 16)
  - Gifts - E, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 17)
  - Gifts - F, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 18)
  - Gifts - G, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 19)
  - Gifts - H, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 20)
  - Gifts - 1, 1949-1954 (Box B10, Folder 21)
  - Gifts - J, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 22)
  - Gifts - K, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 23)
  - Gifts - L, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 24)
  - Gifts - M, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 25)
  - Gifts - N, 1944-1954 (Box B10, Folder 26)
  - Gifts - O, 1944-1953 (Box B10, Folder 27)
  - Gifts - P, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - Q, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 2)
  - Gifts - R, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 3)
  - Gifts - S, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 4)
  - Gifts - T, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 5)
  - Gifts - U, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 6)
  - Gifts - V, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 7)
  - Gifts - W, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 8)
  - Gifts - XYZ, 1944-1954 (Box B11, Folder 9)
  - Scholarships - General, 1944-1948 (Box B11, Folder 10)
  - Margaret Abrams Memorial Scholarship, 1937 (Box B11, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Play Committee Scholarship, 1938 (Box B11, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Scholarship, 1923-1932 (Box B11, Folder 13)
  - American Bankers Association Foundation Scholarship, 1928-1929 (Box B11, Folder 14)
  - American - German Exchange Fellowship, 1927-1931 (Box B11, Folder 15)
  - American Legion Auxiliary Scholarship, 1934 (Box B11, Folder 16)
  - American Smelting and Refining Company Fellowship in Chemistry, 1925-1938 (Box B11, Folder 17)
  - Anglo-California Trust Company Scholarship, 1927-1931 (Box B11, Folder 18)
  - Anonymous Scholarship (from Professor P.J. Treat and Mrs. C.A. Huston), 1924-1934 (Box B11, Folder 19)
  - George P. Baldwin Scholarship, 1924 (Box B11, Folder 20)
  - Adolph Barkan Fund for Research in Medicine, 1936-1939 (Box B11, Folder 21)
  - Dorothoy Bell Research Fund, 1939 (Box B11, Folder 22)
  - B. P. O. Elks (San Francisco Lodge 3) Scholarship, 1931-1936 (Box B11, Folder 23)
  - Bertha Hyde Braly Scholarship, 1916-1931 (Box B11, Folder 24)
  - Douglas Houghton Campbell Fund, 1925 (Box B11, Folder 25)
  - Garvan Scholarship (American Chemical Society), 1937 (Box B11, Folder 26)
  - Buddy Cass Scholarship, 1940 (Box B11, Folder 27)
  - Daughters of the Cincinatti, 1937 (Box B11, Folder 28)
  - Commission for Student Aid Scholarship, 1934-1935 (Box B11, Folder 29)
  - Commission for Student Aid Scholarship, 1935-1936 (Box B11, Folder 30)
  - Commission for Student Aid Scholarship, 1936-1937 (Box B11, Folder 31)
  - Commission for Student Aid Scholarship, 1937-1938 (Box B11, Folder 32)
  - Commission for Student Aid Scholarship, 1938-1939 (Box B11, Folder 33)
  - Commission for Student Aid Scholarship, 1939-1940 (Box B11, Folder 34)
  - William A. Holt Scholarship, 1935-1937 (Box B11, Folder 35)
  - Commonwealth Fund Service Fellowship, 1937 (Box B11, Folder 36)
  - William S. Cranston Memorial Scholarship, 1924-1931 (Box B11, Folder 37)
  - Cubberley Anonymous Scholarship (Prof. Swain), 1932-1935 (Box B11, Folder 38)
  - Jane A. Delano Loan Fund, 1939 (Box B11, Folder 39)
  - Delta Gamma Sorority Scholarship, 1926 (Box B11, Folder 40)
  - Dr. Dutton's Post Graduate Fund, 1939 (Box B11, Folder 41)
  - Cordelia Elkus Scholarship, 1928-1932 (Box B11, Folder 42)
  - East Bay Stanford Women's Club Loan Fund, 1925-1930 (Box B11, Folder 43)
  - Cyril F. Elwell Scholarship in Electrical Engineering, 1920-1925 (Box B11, Folder 44)
  - Encina Club Scholarship, 1935 (Box B11, Folder 45)
  - Encina Club Scholarship, 1927-1928 (Box B11, Folder 46)
  - Faculty Women's Club Scholarship, 1925 (Box B11, Folder 47)
  - George E. Farrand Loan Fund, 1928-1937 (Box B11, Folder 48)
  - Walter Mason Field Scholarship, 1927-1932 (Box B11, Folder 49)
  - Food Machinery Corporation (FMC) Fellowships in Chemistry, 1935-1937 (Box B11, Folder 50)
  - Foster and Kleiser Company Grant, 1937-1938 (Box B11, Folder 51)
    To study school-press relations, for Prof. Rex Harlow, School of Education
  - French Republic Medal, 1935-1938 (Box B11, Folder 52)
  - Richard Friedlander Memorial Loan Fund, 1928-1934 (Box B11, Folder 53)
  - Adaline W. Fuller (Anonymous) Scholarship, 1937-1940 (Box B11, Folder 54)
  - German Scholarship, 1936 (Box B11, Folder 55)
  - Golden Gate International Exposition Scholarship (Leland Cutler), 1938-1939 (Box B11, Folder 56)
  - Gray's Harbor (Wash.) Regional Scholarship, 1921 (Box B11, Folder 57)
  - Wilmer J. Gross Scholarship, 1919-1927 (Box B11, Folder 58)
  - Horace Guittard Scholarship, 1934-1938 (Box B11, Folder 59)
  - Harvard Club of San Francisco Fellowship, 1916 (Box B11, Folder 60)
  - E.W. Hadley Scholarship, 1938 (Box B11, Folder 61)
  - Hammond Lumber Company Fellowship, 1929-1930 (Box B11, Folder 62)
  - Mr. and Mrs. R. P. Hastings, 1934-1938 (Box B11, Folder 63)
  - Theodore J. Hoover Fellowship Fund, 1937 (Box B11, Folder 64)
  - International Commission on Education, 1942-1943 (Box B11, Folder 65)
  - Gift Forms or Trust Forms, 1944-1945 (Box B12, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - General Data, 1944-1959 (Box B12, Folder 2)
  - Gifts - Medical School, 1949-1950 (Box B12, Folder 3)
  - Gifts - Medical School, 1947-1949 (Box B12, Folder 4)
  - Gifts - Medical School, 1944-1946 (Box B12, Folder 5)
  - Prospective Gifts, 1944-1946 (Box B12, Folder 6)
  - Prospective Gifts, 1946-1949 (Box B12, Folder 7)
  - Prospective Gifts, 1942-1946 (Box B12, Folder 8)
  - Prospective Donors, 1944-1948 (Box B12, Folder 9)
  - Gifts - Special End-of-Year Letters, 1945-1946 (Box B12, Folder 10)
  - Gifts - Corrections to Gift Tags, 1944-1946 (Box B12, Folder 11)
  - Hoover Library Special Birthday Fund, 1948 (Box B12, Folder 12)
  - Hoover Library Special Birthday Fund, 1948 (Box B12, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box B12, Folder 14)
  - Gifts- Medical School, 1951-1954 (Box B12, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Board of Directors, 1957-1961 (Box B13, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Financial Data, 1954-1960 (Box B13, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I), 1959-1960 (Box B13, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Minutes and Reports, 1959-1960 (Box B13, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - International Industrial Development Conference, 1957 (Box B13, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.), 1958-1959 (Box B13, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Board Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1958-1959 (Box B13, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Board Minutes and Reports, 1957-1958 (Box B13, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I), 1956-1957 (Box B13, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I), 1957-1958 (Box B13, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Board Minutes and Reports, 1956-1957 (Box B13, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.), 1956 (Box B13, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I), 1955-1956 (Box B13, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I), 1955-1956 (Box B13, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.), 1954-1955 (Box B14, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I), 1953-1954 (Box B14, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Articles and By-Laws, 1946-1949 (Box B14, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box B14, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Board of Directors, 1948-1949 (Box B14, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Fund Raising, 1948-1949 (Box B14, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Literature, 1948-1949 (Box B14, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Brochure, 1949 (Box B14, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Management and Control, 1949 (Box B14, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Program Reports and Future Plans, 1949 (Box B14, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Projects, 1949 (Box B14, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - First Annual Report, 1946-1947 (Box B14, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Stationery, 1949 (Box B14, Folder 13)
  - Armour Research Foundation - Brochure, 1949 (Box B14, Folder 14)
    Located in Illinois
  - Pacific Research Foundation, 1945 (Box B14, Folder 15)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - By-Laws, 1949 (Box B15, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Correspondence by J.E. Hobson, 1950-1955 (Box B15, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Correspondences to D. M. Whitaker, 1950-1952 (Box B15, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Miscellaneous, 1950-1955 (Box B15, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Reports and Summaries to Board of Directors, 1949-1952 (Box B15, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Technical Advisory Committee Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box B15, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Report Prepared by S.R.I., 1954 (Box B15, Folder 7)
    "The Impact of the Aluminum Industry on the Economy of the Pacific Northwest" - Not in a Folder.
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - 9th Meeting of the SRI Associates, 1954 (Box B15, Folder 8)
    Not in a Folder
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I) - Reference Material for the Board of Directors Meetings, 1949-1955 (Box B15, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Research Institute (S.R.I.) - Financial Statements, 1949-1956 (Box B15, Folder 10)
  - Funds - A, 1963-1967 (Box B16, Folder 1)
    List of "A" names on outside of folder
  - Funds - Matt Adler Loan Fund, 1952-1963 (Box B16, Folder 2)
  - Funds - Affiliates Program in Aeronautics and Engineering, 1957-1968 (Box B16, Folder 3)
  - Funds - Affiliates Programs Miscellaneous, 1965-1968 (Box B16, Folder 4)
  - Funds - Business School Affiliates Program, 1960-1964 (Box B16, Folder 5)
  - Funds - Allied Chemical Corporation, 1960-1967 (Box B16, Folder 6)
  - Funds - American Can Company (Scholarship), 1952-1964 (Box B16, Folder 7)
  - Funds - American Medical Education Foundation Fund and National Fund for Medicine Educaiton, 1955-1965 (Box B16, Folder 8)
  - Funds - Alfred Aram Fund, 1965 (Box B16, Folder 9)
  - Funds - Asia Foundation Miscellaneous, 1958-1961 (Box B16, Folder 10)
  - Funds - Asia Foundation Book Fund, 1958-1961 (Box B16, Folder 11)
  - Funds - Asia Foundation Law Fellowship Fund, 1956-1959 (Box B16, Folder 12)
  - Funds - Athletic Department Building Fund, 1961 (Box B16, Folder 13)
  - Funds - Axelson Loan Fund, 1952-1954 (Box B16, Folder 14)
  - Funds - B, 1959-1964 (Box B16, Folder 15)
    List of "B" names on outside of folder
  - Funds - Helen Lucile Bailey Memorial Fund, 1953-1968 (Box B16, Folder 16)
  - Funds - The Bailey Book Fund, 1959-1967 (Box B16, Folder 17)
    Named for Thomas A. Bailey
  - Funds - Barnett Memorial Fund, 1955-1966 (Box B16, Folder 18)
    Named for George DeForest Barnett part of a Medical Center Fund
  - Funds - Baseball Award Fund, 1962 (Box B16, Folder 19)
  - Funds - Edith Wilcox Beasly Trust Fund, 1954 (Box B16, Folder 20)
  - Funds - Bechtel International Student Center, 1963 (Box B16, Folder 21)
  - Funds - Bell Fund, 1961 (Box B16, Folder 22)
    Named for Dr. Daniel Hughes and Helen Clift Bell
  - Funds - Albert M. Bender Memorial Trust Fund, 1941-1960 (Box B16, Folder 23)
  - Funds - Gustav H. and Elizabeth Benkendorf Scholarship Fund, 1955-1963 (Box B16, Folder 24)
  - Funds - August Berner Scholarship, 1945 (Box B16, Folder 25)
  - Funds - E. N. Bernicri Endowment, 1950 (Box B16, Folder 26)
  - Funds - Bethlehem Steel Company - PACE Pledge, 1962 (Box B16, Folder 27)
  - Funds - Bing Medical School Fund, 1956-1964 (Box B16, Folder 28)
  - Funds - Ernest L. Blanck Memorial Fund, 1955-1963 (Box B16, Folder 29)
  - Funds - The John A. Blume and John A. Blume, II Fund, 1956-1967 (Box B16, Folder 30)
  - Funds - Boeing Company - PACE Pledge, 1962-1963 (Box B16, Folder 31)
  - Funds - Boothe Fund, 1961-1964 (Box B16, Folder 32)
    Named for D. Power and Margaret S. Boothe
  - Funds - Boswell Foundation - Agricultural Research Center, 1959-1964 (Box B16, Folder 33)
  - Funds - James G. Boswell Foundation - Loan Funds, 1953-1955 (Box B16, Folder 34)
  - Funds - Bourn Student Fund, 1951-1958 (Box B16, Folder 35)
    Named for John J. and Maud E. Bourn
  - Funds - Guy Chapman Bowman Fund jointly with Herrin Fund, 1963-1964 (Box B16, Folder 36)
  - Funds - Branner Memorial Library Fund, 1923-1964 (Box B16, Folder 37)
  - Funds - Dr. Bravo's Revolving Fund for the Medical Education of a Student of Mexican Extraction, 1947-1956 (Box B16, Folder 38)
  - Funds - Carl Breer Library - Study Facility Fraternity, 1963-1964 (Box B16, Folder 39)
    Earlier funds Memorial Church Spire Restoration
  - Funds - Morgan Lewis Brett, Jr. Music Fund, 1952-1966 (Box B16, Folder 40)
  - Funds - Carl G. Brown Endowment Fund, 1957-1964 (Box B16, Folder 41)
  - Funds - Graduate School of Business Miscellaneous Funds, 1961-1967 (Box B16, Folder 42)
  - Funds - Graduate School of Business Affiliate Program Fund, 1959-1967 (Box B16, Folder 43)
  - Funds - Graduate School of Business Building Fund, 1960-1966 (Box B16, Folder 44)